Tyler CrabtreeEmail: Crabtree.tyler@gmail.comFiles: ResearchScraper.py svm.pySupportVectorReport.pdfResearch.txtReadMe.txtExampleSupportVectorDemo.mp4ExampleScraper.mp4SupportVectorReport(LaTeXFiles).zipDescription svm.py: This provides a simulation of the accuracy of support vector machines. This will provide a GUI showing randomized data with the optimal hyper plane shown. Requirements ResearchScraper.py:*Import numpy.py Description ResearchScraper.py: This is a python program that scrapes Wikipidea’s API. The data is parsed to look for specific information. The title, summary, categories, and reception (if there a reception category to parse) will be shown in terminal. This will quickly form a paper from the searched terms. The stored information will be saved in Research.txt.Requirements ResearchScraper.py:*There is an internet connection.Make sure all of these imports are installed on your machine: *import wikipedia  *import unidecode*import warnings Running Instructions: 1. In the directory with ResearchScraper.py2. $ Python ResearchScrape.py3. While the program is running, type in topics to search.4. Example searches are: “The lion the witch and the wardrobe” or “The Two Gentlemen From Verona” or “Support Vector Machines"  Notes:Feel free to contact my email with any questions pertaining to the code. 